[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMING]
[JUNE] Meet my family.
The Roses.
Yes.
Those Roses!
The owner of the Roses
Restaurant Empire.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
However...
they are my very,
very distant relatives.
Like,
as far as Pluto is
to Planet Earth!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm just waiting
for the manager.
- So I'll know who they gave
- Sir! Sir!
- the check to.
[PING] Excuse me.
Uh...
Please try our product!
I'm sure you'll like it!
You look really stressed.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh!
Served with our homemade
special Ima-Asim Vinegar!
It's really good!
Sir, I checked the office.
Your brother already got
your check!
Here. [PANTING]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Please. Fire her.
Hey, I didn't do anything wrong!
Your presentation of the product
is wrong.
You used Pindang Tocino
to promote your business.
You are so--
Fire!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]